torrentstate.com 2010-06-14

# » Torrent Search at TorrentState.com

**Your Privacy**

TorrentState.com is committed to protecting your privacy. TorrentState.com does not sell, trade or rent your personal information to other companies. TorrentState.com will not collect any personal information about you except when you specifically and knowingly provide such information.  
By using our Web site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by TorrentState.com. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post the changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. Currently, TorrentState.com may provide aggregate statistics about our traffic patterns, and related site information to reputable third-party vendors, but these statistics will include no personal identifying information.

**Third Party Advertising**

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name or email address) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

**Third Party Cookies**

In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser.

**Linked Websites and Files**

If TorrentState.com has provided links or pointers to other websites or files, no inference or assumption should be made and no representation should be implied that TorrentState.com is connected with, operates or controls these websites or files. TorrentState.com is not responsible for the content or practices of third party websites that may be linked to this website. This website may also be linked to other websites operated by companies affiliated or connected with TorrentState.com. When visiting other websites, however, you should refer to each such website's individual Terms of Use and not rely on this Agreement.

**Modification of Privacy Policy**

Torrent-Finder.com reserves the right, at any time, to modify, alter or update the Privacy Policy and you agree to be bound by such modifications, alterations or updates.
